Creating and customizing a table in Doc²,
before a table is automatically taught in Doc²,
can then be read out
the function must first be activated.
To do this, under Settings modules, tables,
extraction can be selected.
Following this, this function is now
active.
Should use a table from the document
must first be read out by Doc²
said document is uploaded and processed there
will.
After opening the document and eventually
Checking the header data must do the tables
Clicked on the icon at the bottom under Article
will.
This brings us to the table view.
There is a small one on the left
Overview of all pages of the document.
And on the basis of this can also be used between pages
be navigated.
The current page is outlined in purple.
In the middle is a display of the current
side of the document while right next to it
the extracted data is displayed.
To create a new table or an existing one
Edit table needs training
mode to be activated.
Hereby we have various processing
opportunities available.
On the one hand, we can go into the ad
search out, and try automatically from
make the system recognize a table.
If the table is to be taught in manually,
the edit button must be activated and then the
desired table can be marked.
With the button etc. markings are added,
marking the different columns.
Subsequent to this, the save
icon is clicked and the detected data will be displayed
shown in the table on the right.
There are several above the table
functions.
These are changes from left to right
cancel.
Advanced settings of.
Can be set the number of times
we delete the data.
Block the extraction of the table for
custom columns for these suppliers
enable add custom column
Edit rows data mode activates this
mode is needed when specific part
data within the fields can be read out
should and special rules if manual
Regex rules should be added.
For the completion of the table need
first the columns are assigned accordingly
will.
Columns should be superfluous or not too
extracted, they can also be deleted
will.
Likewise, superfluous lines with a
click on the X to be removed.
Under the three dots next to the column names
can also be found next to the delete button
Group rows icon rows pin is in
System indicated when a new line begins.
The house number position is recommended here
or to use sum.
Is the content of the table wrong or could
cannot be read out immediately, must go through
one click the appropriate field in the
Table selected and then in the document
the corresponding content also with a
Double-click or a highlight selected
will.
Now let's look at the rows as the work mode
is closer, this can enabled for
extra audible column all that one blue
Have additional data on the heading
future automatic extraction
an additional column is required
can this be added here. For that
Extracting the data needs the appropriate
Field clicked first and then
the desired information on the document
to be chosen.
Are all required data in the table
deposited, the table must be saved and
then be exported.
With the export, the newly created rules
saved and will be saved when uploading the
same data type usually applied immediately.